internationalculinarycenter.com 2012-04-11

# International Culinary Center Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy & Conditions of Use for  
The International Culinary Center, LLC 

Because The International Culinary Center, LLC (The International Culinary Center) wants to demonstrate its commitment to our users' privacy, we have disclosed our information practices for our website below. If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should contact [Tara Hill](mailto:thill@internationalculinarycenter.com) at 888.324.2433. 

For related practices, please read our Conditions of Use.

  * What information does The International Culinary Center collect?
  * How is my information used?
  * What is an IP address and why does The International Culinary Center want that information?
  * What are cookies?
  * What are log files and how are they used?
  * What security exists to protect the information I provide?
  * What happens if The International Culinary Center makes any changes to this privacy policy?
  * How do I contact The International Culinary Center to update/change my information or opt-out of future emails and mailings?

INFORMATION COLLECTION  
The International Culinary Center, LLC is the sole owner of the information collected on www.internationalculinarycenter.com, and www.frenchculinary.com.

The International Culinary Center, LLC collects information from our users at several different points on our web site. 

  * More Info Request  
Registration is not required in order to use this web site. However, a user must first complete the contact/registration form in order to receive information via mail or download brochures online, submit the contact form and/or to apply to The International Culinary Center. To complete the form, a user is required to give contact information including: name, phone number, email address, mailing address, high school or equivalency completion and citizenship status. We use this information to contact the user about the programs and events at The International Culinary Center for which they have expressed interest or are related to this program of interest. If you wish to be removed from these mailings, please follow the instructions at the bottom of each email or use the contact information provided in the section “ Opt-out/Remove” below.  
 
  * Email Sign-Up  
Upon submitting contact or application information, users are added to the email and promotional mailing list. If you wish to be removed from these mailings, please follow the instructions at the bottom of the email or use the contact information provided in the section “ Opt-out/Remove” below. Users are able to sign up to receive separate regular emails about L'Ecole by providing their email address within the L'Ecole section. Members of the press may also do so within the Press area to receive any press announcements via email. As the press email list is limited to members of the press only, users must provide their name, publication and email address at sign up.  
 
  * Applying to The International Culinary Center  
When applying for any program at The International Culinary Center through the online application, users must provide contact information, educational and work history and financial information (credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to enroll the user. If we have trouble processing the deposit payment, the information is used to contact the user. We may also email the applicant about related programs or special events being offered by The International Culinary Center or partners. If you wish to be removed from these mailings, please follow the instructions at the bottom of each email or use the contact information provided in the section “ Opt-out/Remove” below.   
 
  * Information Use  
We do not sell or rent your contact information to third parties except when required to disclose such information by law or in response to a request from a law enforcement agency or authority. The International Culinary Center uses contact information to send the user additional information about our schools and partners. A user's contact information may also be used to contact the user directly.

The International Culinary Center does not seek to solicit information from anyone under the age of thirteen (defined as a child). If a child submits information to us and we know that the person submitting the information is a child, we will not use it for any purpose. We will delete the information as soon as we discover it and we will not disclose it to third parties.

  * Third Party Intermediaries  
We use outside companies to mail some promotional material via email and post. These companies do not retain, share, store, or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.  
 
  * IP Address  
We log all connections to our web servers. Those log files include your IP address. An IP address is NOT personally identifiable information, but general information about your location, connection to the Internet, and your Internet Service Provider. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer the site.   
 
  * Cookies  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about their computer. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. So, while the user session will be tracked to give us an idea of what parts of the site a user is visiting, the user will remain anonymous. If a user rejects cookies, they may still use our site. 

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once a user closes the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. We may use cookies to: 

1\. Keep count of your return visits to our site 

2\. Accumulate and report anonymous, aggregate, statistical information on web site usage 

  * Deliver content specific to your interests  
We do not use cookies to identify, monitor or track any personally identifiable information. Our cookies in and of themselves do not contain any personally identifiable information about you. We do not merge or associate our cookie information with any personally identifiable information we obtain.  
 
  * Log Files  
Like most standard web site servers, we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. This information is not linked to personally identifiable information.  
 
  * Links  
The International Culinary Center web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site, www.internationalculinarycenter.com, and www.frenchculinary.com.   
 
  * Security  
The International Culinary Center takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the web site, their information is protected both online and off-line. 

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with industry standard encryption software - Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to unlocked, or open, when users are just 'surfing'. 

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. The servers that store personally identifiable information are also maintained in a secure environment. 

If users have any questions about the security at our web site, users can send an email to [Tara Hill](mailto:thill@internationalculinarycenter.com). 

  * Notification of Changes  
We will notify all users if there are any material changes to our privacy policy. We will take commercially reasonable measures to obtain written or active email consent from the user if www.internationalculinarycenter.com, or www.frenchculinary.com is going to be using the information collected from the user in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection. All changes to our privacy statement will be posted prior to a change.   
 
  * Contact Us/Opt-Out/Update  
To remove or change your contact information in our database, or to not receive future mailings or other communications, as well as for all other inquiries, please contact us at any time using one of the options below: 

Email [thill@internationalculinarycenter.com](mailto:thill@internationalculinarycenter.com)

Contact us at:  
The International Culinary Center  
Attn: Tara Hill   
462 Broadway  
New York, NY 10013  
1.888.324.2433 

CONDITIONS OF USE  
The International Culinary Center, LLC provides information and services to you subject to the following conditions. If you visit and/or apply online at www.internationalculinarycenter.com, or www.frenchculinary.com you accept these conditions. 

Please review our privacy information, which also governs your visit to www.internationalculinarycenter.com, and www.frenchculinary.com. Questions about The International Culinary Center Conditions of Use or Privacy Practices, please contact [Tara Hill](mailto:thill@internationalculinarycenter.com). 

  * Copyright  
All content included on this site, such as text, graphics, logos, button icons, images, digital downloads, data compilations, and software, is the property of The International Culinary Center (The International Culinary Center) and protected by United States and international copyright laws.   
 
  * Site Content  
The International Culinary Center, LLC attempts to be as accurate as possible. However, www.internationalculinarycenter.com, and www.frenchculinary.com does not warrant that course descriptions, dates and prices or other content of this site is complete or error-free.  
 
  * Comments and Questions  
We welcome your feedback. However, any comments, ideas, notes, messages, suggestions, or other communications sent to the site shall be and remain the exclusive property of The International Culinary Center and we may use all such communications in any manner, including reproducing, disclosing, and publishing such communications, all without compensation to you. 

Should you have any questions or complaints regarding violations of this Agreement, please [contact us](mailto:thill@internationalculinarycenter.com). 

  * License and Site Access  
The International Culinary Center grants you a limited license to access and make personal use of this site and not to download (other than page caching) or modify it, or any portion of it, except with express written consent of The International Culinary Center. This license does not include any resale or commercial use of this site or its contents or any use of data mining, robots, or similar data gathering and extraction tools. This site or any portion of this site may not be reproduced, duplicated, copied, sold, resold, visited, or otherwise exploited for any commercial purpose without express written consent of The International Culinary Center. You may not use any meta tags or any other "hidden text" utilizing The International Culinary Center, LLC’s name or trademarks without the express written consent of The International Culinary Center, LLC. Any unauthorized use terminates the permission or license granted by The International Culinary Center. You are granted a limited, revocable, and non-exclusive right to create a hyperlink to the home page of www.internationalculinarycenter.com, or www.frenchculinary.com, so long as the link does not portray The International Culinary Center in a false, misleading, derogatory, or otherwise offensive matter. You may not use any logo of The International Culinary Center or other proprietary graphic or trademark as part of the link without express written permission. To request permission, please contact [Tara Hill](mailto:thill@internationalculinarycenter.com).
